Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ fortuneugochukwu (LinkedIn)

Top Skills BLS

Hospitals
Acute Care

Fortune Ugochukwu

Cardiology Nurse Practitioner at Medical City Healthcare (Formerly HCA North Texas)

Wylie, Texas

Summary

I am a Doctor of Nursing Practice prepared and an experienced Adult Gerontology Acute Care and Family Nurse Practitioner with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. I am skilled in Medical Assessment, diagnosis, treatment of adult, and pediatrics patients. Patient advocacy, nursing education, patient education, multiple procedural skills, management of patients with both critical and chronic conditions are essential aspects of my job. I am a strong healthcare services professional with multispecialty experience and currently practicing as a Cardiology, Cardiothoracic Surgery and Hospitalist Nurse Practitioner.

-Nene Fortune Ugochukwu, DNP, MSN, APRN, AGACNP-BC, FNP-BC, CCRN.

Experience

Medical City Healthcare (Formerly HCA North Texas) Cardiology ED/ Cardiothoracic Surgery Nurse Practitioner February 2020 - Present (4 months)

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Sound Physicians
Hospitalist Nurse Practitioner
February 2020 - Present (4 months)

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Envision Physician Services Hospitalist Nurse Practitioner May 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month)

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

ComplexCare Solutions
Nurse Practitioner
May 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month)

UT Southwestern Medical Center

Nurse Practitioner

August 2015 - April 2018 (2 years 9 months)

Richardson/Plano Clinics

Primary care services: acute to chronic health management.

LuminCARE

Nurse Practitioner

May 2016 - February 2018 (1 year 10 months)

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Nurse Practitioner duties at an Urgent care/Family Practice clinic

Questcare Partners

Nurse Practitioner

January 2015 - December 2015 (1 year)

Plano, Texas

Nurse Practitioner for Quest Care Hospitalist @ The Medical Center of Plano

Tenet Healthcare

Critical Care Nurse

August 2006 - May 2015 (8 years 10 months)

Medical City Healthcare (Formerly HCA North Texas)

Critical Care Nurse

March 2008 - March 2014 (6 years 1 month)

Dallas, Texas

Medical City Dallas Hospital

Education

University of Arkansas

DNP, Specialization in AGACNP · (2016 - 2019)

Walden University

MSN, Specialization in Family Nurse practitioner · (2012 - 2014)

Midwestern State University

BSN, Initial Licensure, Registered Nurse · (2004 - 2006)

Eastfield College

Associate of Arts and Sciences (AAS), General Studies · (2001 - 2005)

University of Arkansas
MSN, Nurse Educator student · (2018)